Bruna Soares

Senior Campaign Manager

<u>bsoares.fs@gmail.com</u> • +55 (011) 97214- 7072 São Paulo, Brazil

With over 10 years of experience in Campaign Management and Customer Service Success within AdTech industry, I've developed a profound skillset in digital operations setting up, testing, and monitoring ad campaigns. I have made significant contributions to identifying strategies that support business goals. My career achievements include notable improvements in operational efficiency and recognition for resolving complex issues. I have also successfully coordinated digital marketing strategies across over 20 territories in Latin America.

Career Experience

Spotify, São Paulo Senior Traffic Manager January 2023 — July 2024

- · Latin America Lead in the digital marketing campaigns management for Labels;
- Managed ad campaigns in more than 15 territories for labels such as Universal Music, Sony Music, and Warner Music across the Spotify platform;
- Analyzed campaign performance data, providing insights and advised for optimization;
- Collaborated with sales and other internal teams to ensure alignment of ad operations with business.

Music2!/Mynd, São Paulo

June 2018 — December 2022

Ad Solutions Coordinator

- Created strategic sales planning, inventory forecasting and utilization, ad product pricing and packaging;
- Partnered with sales and revenue operations teams, presenting media proposals in the pre-sale process for renowned brands like Apple, Procter & Gamble, Red Bull, Pernod Ricard, Diageo, Itaú, Sanofi Brasil, playing a key role in the success of 50+ advertising campaigns annually;
- Assisted marketing team meetings to provide insight on pricing, packaging, and inventory requirements for media proposals and integration products;
- Collaborated with Sales and Ad Ops team to address delivery issues and suggest inventory solutions.

VEVO, São Paulo

March 2016 — May 2018

Senior Account Manager

- Supported top-performing Account Executives, working closely with advertising agencies and prestigious brands;
- Handled 15+ accounts like Coca-Cola, Mondelez, Heineken, GM, Dell, ensuring their campaigns were aligned with the business objectives, leading to improved customer satisfaction;
- Managed R\$20M annual budget, resulting in the retention of 85% campaign viewers
- Partnered with marketing team department to help manage client sponsorships, integrations and added value;
- Worked with international teams Yield, Research & Marketing to fulfill RFPs and fully execute IOs.

Predicta, São Paulo

August 2012 — February 2016

Junior Campaign Manager

 Executed advertising campaigns using ad management platforms such as DFP, DBM, and Predicta Attract Ad Management;

- Ensured creatives adhered to technical specifications, including thorough testing and troubleshooting on rich media, flash, and video to run successfully and accurately;
- · Analyzed reports as needed including forecasting and delivery.

XPG, São Paulo August 2011 — July 2012

Marketing Communication Assistant

- Responsible for product promotion activities, and implementation of visual and written communication standards;
- · Set up and monitoring of ad campaigns in the XPG and partner websites;
- Run and analyze reports as needed including forecasting and delivery.

Education

Master of Business Management and Digital Media ESPM, São Paulo

Bachelor's Degree in Communication and Media FIAM-FAAM, São Paulo

Skills

Advertising • Strategic Panning • Campaign Management • Account Management • Data Literacy • Data Analysis • Customer Service Problem Solving • Communication with clients • Decision Making • MS Office Suite • Ad Management Platforms • CRM (Salesforce) Reporting • Performance Metrics